Guide to the Sports Information Office Records, 1932-ongoing UA.13.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- UA2013-0034, 1927-2015
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs North Carolina, 2004-03-06 (Box UA2013-0034.219)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs Georgetown; Duke vs Florida State, January 24, 2004; January 29, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.219)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.219)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2004-02-01 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2003-11-01 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2003-12-01 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2004-01-01 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1992; 1995 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Photos, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
    Includes 11 digital disks, processed by Digital Records Archivist.
  - Women's Lacrosse: Photos, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
    Includes 6 digital disks, processed by Digital Records Archivist.
  - Women's Lacrosse: Photos, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
    Includes 8 digital disks, processed by Digital Records Archivist.
  - Women's Lacrosse: Photos, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
    Includes 7 digital disks, processed by Digital Records Archivist.
  - Cross Country: Photos, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Swimming: Photos, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
    Includes 8 digital disks and a computer disk, processed by Digital Records Archivist.
  - Gold Medal Carla Overbeck, 1996 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Women's Basketball: Photos, 1998-1999 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Jay and Katie Heaps, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Baseball: Ryan Jackson; Quinton McCracken, 2000-05-01 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Championship Game, 1999 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. St. Joe, 1996-11-01 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. UNC, 1999 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Men's Soccer: Duke vs. Wisconsin, 1995-12-10 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Duke vs. Notre Dame, 1995 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Tournament, 1998 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Men's Basketball: Final Four Charlotte, 1994 (Box UA2013-0034.220)
  - Cross Country, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.221)
  - Assorted Optical Media, 2000; 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.221)
  - Maryland vs Duke, 2005-10-07 (Box UA2013-0034.221)
    Access note. Collection contains fragile audiovisual/photographic formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
    Includes AV materials.
  - NCAA College Cup Semifinal: Duke vs UCSB, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.221)
  - Women's Basketball: Photos, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.221)
    Includes photographic negatives and digital disks.
  - Women's Basketball: Photos, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.221)
  - Women's Basketball: Photos, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.221)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.221)
  - Men's Basketball, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.221)
  - Assorted Optical Media, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.221)
  - Track and Field, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Tennis, 2003-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Assorted Optical Media, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Virtue, Tucker, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Joe Tkac, 2007-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Sam Spillane, 2007-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Michael Hutchings, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: James Goldberg, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Edward Cotty, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Thomas Clute, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Michael Catalino, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Max Wygod, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Daniel Theodoris, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Sam Solie, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Stephen Schoeffel, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Devon Sherwood, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Sam Payton, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Jonathan Livadas, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Terence Molinari, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Miller Hughes, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Virginia Cotty, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Sarah Buland, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Christie Barnes, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Betsey Sauer, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Morgan Miller, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Catherine Krom, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Danielle Kachulis, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Lindsay Gilbride, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Sara Giedgowd, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Taylor Fleming, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Christie Klauberg, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Christie Kaestner, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Jillian Heinz, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Miller Hughes, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Caroline Spearman, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Matthew Anderson, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: William McKee, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Parker McKee, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Kevin Young, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Jesse Fehr, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Max Quinzani, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.222)
  - Men's Cross Country and Track and Field: Clippings, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Swimming and Diving: Programs, 2004-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Patti Frost, circa 2004-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Colton Lymer, circa 2004-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Emily Kelly, circa 2004-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Emily Lang, circa 2004-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Kaitlin Rau, circa 2004-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Jessica Perry, circa 2004-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Alex Namba, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Emily McClintock, circa 2004-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Clippings, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Media Guides and Photos, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Men's Cross Country: Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Field Hockey: Media Guides, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Field Hockey: Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Christine Casey, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Kelsey Duryea, circa 2004-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Cassi Carley, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Regan Bosch, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Clippings, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Field Hockey: Jordan Miller, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Field Hockey: Susan Ferger, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Field Hockey: Sarah Schoffstall, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Tennis: Clippings, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Lacrosse: Pictures, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Field Hockey: Clippings, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Field Hockey: Clippings, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Men's Basketball: Statistics, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Assorted Programs and Questionnaires, circa 2004-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Football: Luther Dempsey, 1941 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
    Includes photographic negatives.
  - Field Hockey: Mia Wise, 2014 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Men's Tennis: Photos, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Football: Photos and Stats, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Player Photos, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos and Rules, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Miscellaneous Disks, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.223)
  - Women's Soccer: Katie Otylia Walter, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Soccer: Sara Murphy, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Soccer: Gretchen Miller, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Soccer: Marybeth Kreger, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Soccer: KayAnne Gummersall, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Soccer: Carey Goodman, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Soccer: Kendall Bradley, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Soccer: Jane Alukonis, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Soccer: Rebecca Allen, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Basketball: Janee Johnson, circa 1980-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Golf: Releases, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Golf: Results, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Golf: Rankings, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Basketball: Releases, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Basketball: Ranking, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Soccer: Releases, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Soccer: Rankings, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Soccer: Box Scores, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Braxton Deaver, 2014 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Sean Brady, 2007-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Brandon Allen, 2007-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Zach Howell, 2007-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Tom Montelli, 2007-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Jason Orlando, 2007-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Tom Ryan, 2007-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - ACC Sports Media CDs, 1998-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Football: Programs and Media Guides, 2000-2001 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Golf: Photos, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Men's Basketball: Programs and Guides, 2000-2001 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke Interactive, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Baseball: Guide, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Basketball: Guide and Program, 2000-2001 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Wrestling: Media Guide, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Volleyball: Media Guide, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
    Includes digital and computer disks.
  - Sports Information Materials, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Unlabeled Optical Media, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.224)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2010-03-05 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2010-03-06 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State, 2010-03-07 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Hampton, 2010-03-20 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. LSU, 2010-03-22 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. San Diego State, 2010-03-27 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Baylor, 2010-03-29 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke Blue vs. White Scrimmage, 2009-10-25 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke Blue vs. White Scrimmage Scorebook, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wingate, 2009-11-05 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Alaska Anchorage, 2009-11-08 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Houston Baptist, 2009-11-13 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Texas A&M, 2009-11-15 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Southern, 2009-11-19 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Charlotte, 2009-11-23 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs Western Kentucky, 2009-11-26 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Marquette, 2009-11-27 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Ohio State, 2009-12-03 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Southern California, 2009-12-06 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Stanford, 2009-12-15 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. James Madison, 2009-12-18 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maine, 2009-12-21 (Box UA2013-0034.225)
  - Swimming: Oversize Photographs, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.226)
  - Football: Clippings Book, 1960-1986 (Box UA2013-0034.227)
  - Football: Poster of Field, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.227)
  - Football: Thaddeus Lewis, NFL Debut, 2012-12-30 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Men's Tennis, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Long, Jordan, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Josh Brewer, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Cross Country: Will Leister, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Cross Country: Guillermo Echarte, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Cross Country: Stephen Clark, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Tony Shirk, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Michael Barbas, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Caleb Duncanson, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Staff: Helfer, Sarah, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Women's Tennis: Clippings, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Men's Soccer: Polls, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Men's Soccer: Polls, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Stephen Castiglione, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Men's Cross Country/Track and Field: Greg Dixon, 2015 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Evan Rubinson, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Sport Unknown: Jonathan Sanchez, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Field Hockey: Megan Deakins, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Women's Track and Field: Daryn Howard, 2015 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Adrianne Soo, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Women's Track and Field: Lindsey Huth, 2015 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Men's Track and Field: John Austin, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Cross Country: Andrew Brodeur, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Austin Carpenter, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Cross Country: Joseph Elsakr, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Cross Country: James Kostelnik, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Matt Marriott, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Bo Waggoner, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Brendon Pierson, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Cross Country: Dominick Robinson, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Michael Rowland, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Michael Schalino, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Women's Track and Field: Sonora Williams, 2015 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Esther Vermeer, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Amanda Truelove, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Sophia Treakle, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: LaCresha Styles, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Emily Schwitzer, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Carly Seymour, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Cydney Ross, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Nicole Ragucci, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Leslie Morrison, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Emily Mattoon, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Mary Carleton Johnston, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Andrea Hopkins, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Virginia Hine, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Kayla Hale, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field: Amy Fryt, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Suejin Ahn, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.228)
  - Football: Thaddeus Lewis, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.229)
- UA2014-0056, 1927; 1937; 2016-2017
  This accession contains a large amount of material covering several decades and multiple sports, and includes clippings and other materials, as well as many individual player files.
  - Wrestling, 2013-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.1 (230))
  - Women's Golf, 2014 (Box UA2014-0056.1 (230))
  - Women's Soccer, 2014 (Box UA2014-0056.1 (230))
  - Volleyball, 2012-2013 (Box UA2014-0056.1 (230))
  - Player Files (Football, Swimming/Diving), 2012-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.1 (230))
  - Baseball, 2014 (Box UA2014-0056.2 (231))
  - Men's Tennis, 2013-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.2 (231))
  - Men's Golf, 2014 (Box UA2014-0056.2 (231))
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2014 (Box UA2014-0056.2 (231))
  - Player Files (Volleyball, Men's Golf, Field Hockey, Men's Tennis, Football), 2012-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.2 (231))
  - Baseball, 2013 (Box UA2014-0056.3 (232))
  - Football, 2013 (Box UA2014-0056.3 (232))
  - Track/Cross-Country Clippings, 2011-2013 (Box UA2014-0056.3 (232))
  - Field Hockey, 2013 (Box UA2014-0056.3 (232))
  - Player Files (Rowing), 2012-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.3 (232))
  - Swimming/Diving, 2013-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.4 (233))
  - Rowing, 2013-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.4 (233))
  - Player Files (Rowing, Men's Soccer, Wrestling, Field Hockey, Women's Lacrosse, Men's Basketball, Swimming/Diving, Women's Fencing), 2012-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.4 (233))
  - Women's Fencing Clippings, 2008-2011 (Box UA2014-0056.5 (234))
  - Football, 2013 (Box UA2014-0056.5 (234))
  - Women's Basketball Clippings, 2013-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.5 (234))
  - Player Files (Women's Fencing, Swimming/Diving, Women's Basketball, Women's Soccer), 2012-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.5 (234))
  - Men's Basketball Clippings, 2013-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.6 (235))
  - Women's Tennis, 2013-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.6 (235))
  - Player Files (Men's Lacrosse, Men's Fencing, Men's Basketball, Rowing, Women's Fencing), 2012-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.6 (235))
  - Mike Kryyzewski, 2013-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.7 (236))
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2011 (Box UA2014-0056.7 (236))
  - Player Files (Men's Fencing, Track/Cross Country, Football, Women's Tennis, Women's Fencing), 2012-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.7 (236))
  - Men's Basketball: Recruits, 2012-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.8 (237))
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2010-2012 (Box UA2014-0056.8 (237))
  - Player Files (Women's Fencing, Men's Soccer, Men's Golf), 2012-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.8 (237))
  - Women's Fencing: Clippings, 2011-2012 (Box UA2014-0056.9 (238))
  - Fencing, 2013-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.9 (238))
  - Men's Gold, 2013-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.9 (238))
  - Player Files (Baseball, Men's Golf, Men's Basketball, Women's Tennis, Men's Soccer, Wrestling, Men's Basketball), 2012-2014 (Box UA2014-0056.9 (238))
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2013 (Box UA2014-0056.10 (239))
- UA2015-0051, 1956; 1973-1989; 2013-2016
  - Women's Basketball: Game Files, 2013-2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.24)
  - Track & Field, 2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.24)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.24)
  - Cross Country, 2013 (Box UA.2015-0051.24)
  - Coach Cutcliffe, 2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.25)
  - Duke Football, 2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.25)
  - Player Files (Football), 2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.25)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Files, 2013-2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Files, 2013-2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.27)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Files, 2013-2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.28)
  - Football: Game Programs, 2013-2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.29)
  - Basketball: Newspaper Clippings, 2013-2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.30)
  - Coach K 900th and 1000th win newspaper clippings, 2013-2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.31)
  - Men's Basketball: National Championship newspaper clippings, memorabilia, magazines, etc., 2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.32)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, Player Files, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.33)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Files, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.34)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Files, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.35)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Files, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.36)
  - Field Hockey, 2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.37)
  - Rowing, 2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.37)
  - Men's Tennis, 2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.37)
  - Player Files (Swimming/Diving, Men's Tennis), 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.37)
  - M/W Swimming and Diving, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.38)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.38)
  - Women's Soccer, 2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.38)
  - Women's Basketball, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.38)
  - Women's Golf, 2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.38)
  - Player Files (Women's Basketball, Women's Soccer), 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.38)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Files, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.39)
  - Men's Soccer, 2014 (Box UA.2015-0051.40)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.40)
  - Player Files (Men's Lacrosse), 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.40)
  - Men's Basketball: Recruits, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.41)
  - Cross Country/Track and Field: Clippings, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.41)
  - Fencing: Clippings, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.41)
  - Player Files (Women's Basketball, Baseball, Women's Lacrosse), 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.41)
  - Former Duke Staff, 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.41)
  - Football: Game Files, 2013 (Box UA.2015-0051.42)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Files, Feburary-March 2014-2015 (Box UA.2015-0051.43)
  - Football: Game Files, October-November 2013 (Box UA.2015-0051.43)
  - Football: Play by Play, 2013 (Box UA.2015-0051.44)
  - International Track Programs (From Al Buehler's Office), circa 1973-1974 (Box UA.2015-0051.45)
  - Athlete Photos, 1973-1989 (Box UA.2015-0051.45)
  - Athlete Post Grad Newspaper Clippings, circa 2013 (Box UA.2015-0051.45)
  - Football: Clippings from News and Observer, 1973-1989 (Box UA.2015-0051.45)
  - Game Programs, Ticket Stubs, and Buttons, circa 1980s (Box UA.2015-0051.45)
  - Track and Field: NCAA Championship Newspaper Clippings, 1990 (Box UA.2015-0051.45)
  - Invitational Results, 1988-1989 (Box UA.2015-0051.45)
  - Track: Results, 1989 (Box UA.2015-0051.46)
  - USA Russia Track Meet-Miscellaneous Documents, 1974 (Box UA.2015-0051.46)
  - Cross Country: Results, 1963 (Box UA.2015-0051.46)
  - ITA Meet Operational Documents, 1975 (Box UA.2015-0051.46)
  - Invitational Schedule, 1983 (Box UA.2015-0051.46)
  - Football: Clippings, circa 1980s (Box UA.2015-0051.46)
  - Men's Soccer: Player Files, 2015-2016 (Box UA.2015-0051.46)
  - Men's Basketball: Championship newspapers and magazines, 2010 (Box UA.2015-0051.47)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. International Freedom Games scrapbook, 1973 (Box UA.2015-0051.48)
  - Pan Africa USA International Track Meet scrapbook, 1971 (Box UA.2015-0051.49)
  - Posters from Al Buehler's office, 1956-1999 (Box 1)
- UA2016-0035, 1938-2016
  - Baseball: Brian McAfee (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Baseball: Kellen Urbon (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Baseball: Will Benson (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Baseball: Trent Swart (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Baseball: Conner Stevens (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Baseball: Chris Koppenhaver (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Baseball: Sarkis Ohanian (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Field Hockey, 2015 (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Football: Clippings, 2015 (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Staff: James Weiner (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Staff: Thomas Wade (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Football/Staff: Scottie Montgomery (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Staff: Kyle Mumma (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))
  - Staff: Dalton Moberly (Box 289 (UA2016-0035.1))